Create a Scenario based program on Course Registration System using HashMap where multiple students can be added in a particular course.
[See the Test cases].

In the HashMap, Course Name will be the HashMap key, where as List<String>
will become HashMap value.

Coding Requirements :
---------------------
Take an ELC class CourseRegistration with main method.

In this main method create one HashMap object which takes Course name(String) as a key and Students name (List<String>) as a value.

Create Scanner class object to perform various operation on CourseRegistration system by using switch case.


--- Course Registration Menu ---
1. Register student to course [use V computeIfAbsent(key, Function<T,R>)]
2. Remove student from course [use V computeIfPresent(key, BiFunction<T,U,R>)]
3. View course-wise student list
4. Exit
Enter your choice:  


Test Cases for Output :
-----------------------
Test Case 1 :
-------------
--- Course Registration Menu ---
1. Register student to course
2. Remove student from course
3. View course-wise student list
4. Exit
Enter your choice: 1
Enter course name: Java
Enter student name: Raj
Raj registered to Java

--- Course Registration Menu ---
1. Register student to course
2. View course-wise student list
3. Remove student from course
4. Exit
Enter your choice: 2

 Course → Students List:
Java → [Ravi, Ankita, Sneha]
HTML → [Raj, Rohit]
Python → [Scott, Smith]

--- Course Registration Menu ---
1. Register student to course
2. View course-wise student list
3. Remove student from course
4. Exit
Enter your choice: 3
Enter course name: HTML
Enter student name to remove: Raj
Raj : has removed from HTML


--- Course Registration Menu ---
1. Register student to course
2. View course-wise student list
3. Remove student from course
4. Exit
Enter your choice: 4
Exiting Course Registration System.
