Q1) Create a record called Trainer where components are id, name, salary and experience in years.

Create an ELC class TrainerComparable with main method.

Inside this main method create Trainer array with dynamic size and dynamic array initialization using Scanner class. 


Q2) Create a record called Customer, which accepts id, name and bill as a component.

Create an ELC class CustomerComparator with main method.

Inside this main method create a Customer array with dynamic size and dynamic array initialization using Scanner class. 

Sort the Customer object based on following criteria :

  a) By using Customer id
  b) By using Customer name
  c) By using Customer bill